Chandra Sekhar Jami

5th Floor, Raja Ratnam Towers, Facor Layout, Visakhapatnam-530003

Handheld Nos: +91-9885-535353/ 9849124800 Email ID: <u>jamichandrasekhar1979@gmail.com</u> Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ichnolite/

Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100001712566297



SKILLS & CORE COMPETENCIES:

- Brand Builder | Guerrilla Marketer & GTM Strategist | Team Building & Management
- Global Marketing & Procurement | 10x revenue strategist | B2B, B2C, B2G Sales
- Competitor Analysis | Risk Management | Market Research & Analysis
- Partner/ Vendor Acquisitions

I am a 19 years experienced seasonal marketing professional and Visionary Entrepreneur who has seen crests & troughs in job & business verticals, currently looking forward to work with a progressive product/ services/ manufacturing company in the role of senior management basing on my skillsets & abilities to fulfil any role offered, with passion, integrity, honesty and commitment.

I recently quit from all my 12 years of Entrepreneurship for many reasons including Covid19, fulfilling tax compliances, backstabbing of employee and partner. Now left with serious responsibilities including a recent newbie.

EDUCATION:

B.Tech in Computer Science & Information Technology from M/s Adams Engineering College, Paloncha, Khammam Dist. A.P.,

Diploma in Civil Engineering from M/s AANM & VVRSR Polytechnic, Gudlavalleru, Krishna Dist. A.P.,

BUSINESS CAREER:

Founder & MD- M/s Workswell Metals India Pvt. Ltd., Headquartered at Vizag-AP, with branches in Bhavnagar-Gujarat, Kalyan-Mumbai, Adayar-TN and Hyderabad-TS., during Aug 2016 to till date primarily into manufacturing of Industrial & Automotive Lubricant oils, Petrochemical products, importing & trading of Metals & Minerals globally.

Founder & MD- M/s Workswell Softsys India Pvt. Ltd with Headquartered at Vizag is into Software and Mobile application development since Feb 2016- till date serving Asia Pacific, European and Middle East clients.

Founder & MD- M/s JCS Oil Industries Pvt. Ltd headquartered at Vizag, primarily into trading of Edible and Non Edible oils during Dec 2017 to till date.

Founder & CEO- M/s Ichnolite Technologies, headquarted at Vizag primarly a flagship firm since 2009 to till date primarily into distribution of Security & Surveillance products across A.P., Odisha and Chattisgarh territories.

Founder & CEO- Mototrace.com, a fleet management business subsidiary of the Workswell group which is into Telematics and GPS mapping services.

Founder & CEO- Housingqueen.com, a real estate portal catering Buy, Sell, Renting, Leasing of properties across AP, TS, MH, TN and TS states. Our major clients include reputed Top-10 builders of respective states and buyers are majority NRI clientele.

JOB CAREER:

Post completion of my Diploma, I started my career as Marketing Executive at M/s Varun Motors Pvt. Ltd., Visakhapatnam, A.P., in selling Maruti cars and JTM/TATA cellular solutions during 1998-2002. Then after got an opportunity and joined my Engineering in 2002-2006.

Post engineering, Joined M/s Brigade Corporation India Pvt. Ltd., as a call center executive in providing Technical support to International consumers of HP & Compaq products. Rose to Asst. Manager level where I used to manage 600 agents under me during 2006-2008.

Post that, joined M/s Infronics Systems Ltd., Visakhapatnam as Business Development Manager selling B2B, B2C and B2G enterprise software solutions and got promoted to Sr. B.D.M in less than 3 months during 2008-2009. In 2009, I started my own enterprise named M/s Ichnolite Technologies, since I trusted that I have greater abilities that I can deliver and then never looked back till time.

Has undertaken prestigious national largest projects like AADHAAR, RSBY-(Rashtriya Swayam Bhima Yojana) as sub contract from three limited companies of Hyderabad and enrolled more than 55 Lakh citizens across A.P., Karnataka and Bihar during 2011 and 2014 which I believe to be a greatest achievement till date.

PERSONAL PARTICULARS

Marital Status: Lately, but happily married & blessed with baby boy-"Sahasransh" recently.

Language Fluencies: Telugu, Hindi, English

Location Preferred: Visakhapatnam, as I wanted to be with parents till end of their lives, sacrificing personal career & growth.

Hobbies: International Trading, rearing 5 cows & 5 doggies at present, Interacting with senior businessmen, networking, spend most of the time over internet.

Date of Birth: 20th August 1980 as per records, but actual is 19th September 1979

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

1) Salary expected: Willing to perform first and then demand.

2) Earliest Date of Joining / Notice Period : Immediate

3) Current Company and Location: Workswell Group, Vizag-AP, Bhavnagar-Gujarat.

4) Current Designation : Founder & Managing Director

5) Education Qualification: Graduate

6) Total Work Experience: 19 Years

7) Willing to relocate: No, as I have commitments and need to be with family.

Thank you very much for your time and consideration. I look forward for your positive response and eagerly awaiting to serve your esteemed organization at the earliest. Kindly find my cover letter as a continuation to my resume.

Yours Sincerely,

Chandra Sekhar Jami.

COVER LETTER

To,

The Human Resource Manager.

Dear Sir/Madam,

Greetings for the day. I am privileged to introduce myself as Chandra Sekhar Jami, a seasoned Marketing professional and visionary entrepreneur with 7 years of Job experience and 12 years of Entrepreneurial experience. I believe that I have gained proficient expertise in business consulting, Market Intelligence, Sales & Business development, new brand development, overseas marketing, global procurement and well aware of Organizational goals/ needs and what it demands for every role being offered.

Nature wise, I am Proactive, Enthusiastic, Detail-Oriented, Committed, Adaptive, Focused, Deadline-Driven and Accomplished Individual who accepts and wins majority of every challenge, life throws at us.

I have seen inside out of businesses and well aware of what any organization expects from a resource it deploys. Though my career graph looks little abnormal or irregular to any HR personnel, I am confident that I can excel in any tailor-made role being offered to me, that I will strive my 100% best to achieve.

Henceforth, I am at your disposal any point of time, to discuss about how I can excel and justify to fit in the senior position or how I can impact the KRAs required for the role. I am available on +91-9885-535353/ 9849124800 / jamichandrasekhar1979@gmail.com.

Looking forward for a positive revert to hear from you as well with an obsession to serve your organization at the earliest.

With best regards,

Chandra Sekhar Jami.